让我把这件事情说说清楚
Let me make one thing clear.
你们两个这是最后一次对调身份
This was the last switch-a-Rooney.
你们六岁那年这么折腾过一次
You did it when you were 6.
然后我在你们两个额头上都
And I wrote your names on your forehead
拿记号笔写了你们的名字
in permanent marker.
你们别逼我再这么来一次
Don't make me do that again.
对哦  发箍之夏
Ah, yes... the summer of headbands.
话说回来  我们当时的发箍造型都不错呢
To be fair, though, we rocked the headband look.
哈  哈  有趣
Ha ha fun fun.
玛蒂  你 17 岁之前不允许考驾照
Maddie, no license till you're 17.
看你这个造型怎么拗
Rock that look.
17 岁  真的
17?! Seriously?
莫非你想等到 18 岁再说
You want to make it 18?
啊  17 岁啊  等不及了
Ah, 17. Looking forward to it.
还有  丽芙
And Liv,
既然你这么喜欢开车
since you like driving so much,
在我通知你之前你是我的私人司机
you are now my personal chauffeur until further notice.
- 不要啊  - 没错
- No! - Yes.
万事不算小  万里不称遥
There is no errand too small, no trip too far.
或许我只是出门拿个报纸
I might even have you take me down to the end of the driveway
也会要你开车载我
just to get the newspaper.
我不知道你们怎么看
I don't know.
没错  孩子们
That's right, girls.
我刚刚投下了一个巨型老妈弹
I just dropped an atomic mom bomb.
嘭
Boom!
她这话不当真吧
She can't be serious about that, right?
我们真的到现在还
Do we seriously still get newspapers
有订报纸上门
delivered to our house?
不过你在纳威店里表现不错
Hey, whatever you did down at Neville's totally worked.
有个叫孤狼粉丝发起了联署
Some fanboy named lone wolf started a petition
想要片方让我出演特里斯坦
to get me the role of Tristan.
你成功的说服了粉丝们
You won over the fanboys.
谢谢了
Thank you.
我能确定孤狼就是乔伊
Pretty sure lone wolf is actually lone Joey.
你应该去谢谢他的
You should go thank him.
等等  我记得你不是说乔伊
Wait, I thought you said that Joey
是哪个想要破坏我们的人么
was the one trying to sabotage us.
这事说来话长啊
It was a long and complicated day.
了解
Got it.
还有  很抱歉我搞砸了你的驾照考试
Also I'm sorry about wrecking your driver's test.
真的砸了  哈
Literally. Ha!
我给你带来了一个纪念品
And I got you something.
你应该把这个去还给胡佛家
You might want to return this to the... hoovers.
谢了
Thanks.
想起来了
That reminds me.
我也有个东西要给你
I got you something as well.
亚蒂的狼尾巴
One of Artie's wolf tails. Yeah.
哦  还有  你今年舞会有舞伴了
Oh! Also I got you a date to the prom.
对哦
Yeah.
亚蒂想知道你到时候打算穿什么
Artie would like to know what kind of dress
你是打算穿法师装  还是飞马装
you will be wearing... Wizard or Pegasus?